blueskyscrubs.com 2009-03-31

# Privacy Policy | blue sky scrubs

Updated June 20, 2008

## Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

## The Information We Collect:

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the blue sky scrubs™ website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number  
Credit Card/Payment Information  
(etc.)

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you use the "Tell A Friend" feature on any page to notify a person about this website. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:

Name  
Email address  
(etc.)

## How We Use Information:

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to fulfill the request for which you provided the information. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that request.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

You can register with our website if you would like to receive mailings as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you have checked the appropriate box during checkout, or explicitly entered your contact information using an opt-in form on our website. You are free to add or remove your contact information from this list at any time.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

## Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## How To Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting blue sky scrubs directly. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

## How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at .
